The kettle and the idol
Well, it's early and we are at the end of the show.
I would like to ask Mr. Nakao to make an announcement.
The SILICE EBISCHE ABISH AX SPRING TOUR 2023 100% EBISM is actually underway.
It is going around the country until July 16, so please come and visit us. We are looking forward to seeing you.
Please come and visit us.
And one more thing to say,
The annual summer event of Ebichu, Famien, will be held again this year.
We will be performing at Lake Yamanaka on August 5 and 6,
This live show will have a lot of water and we will be able to enjoy the summer to the fullest,
Please come and join us. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
It's going to be a lot of fun. Famien.
Famien is fun.
How many times are we going to have it at Lake Yamanaka?
We have been playing at Lake Yamanakako for a long time.
Sometimes we go to Kawaguchi Lake,
Oh, you have Kawaguchi Lake there?
That's the first one,
I had an image of Lake Yamanaka.
We start from Kawaguchi Lake and go down to Yamanakako,
Wow.
The members of the band make their own menus and sell them outside the venue,
It's a fun summer concert, isn't it?
I am looking forward to it.
Mr. Nakayama was given a gift of tea by Yoru-kun to cheer him up at the end of the show,
Today it is tea.
I love tea.
Really?
Yes, I love tea. Tea.
No, but it's tough. You're new, Yamanaka-san.
Be sure.
By all means.
Yes, by all means. Bon appétit.
You're 23 years old now, Riko.
Bon appétit.
And many other things.
What do you think?
It warms me up.
Does it warm you up?
No, I think you've given me the most honest answer.
Thank you very much.
So how was it?
I've spoken five times this week.
I like to listen to other people's stories, but I am not very good at talking about myself.
I see. But how is that surprising? I'm not so good at talking about myself.
It's the same when I do interviews.
I don't know... I think I'm not very good at talking about myself.
The episodes themselves are very interesting.
Thank you very much.
It's interesting.
But to be honest, I don't want to say that much about myself.
I love to listen to other people's stories.
I love listening to other people's stories.
I see. That's how Mr. Nakayama was.
Please give a cute closing to the camera.
Yes.
Please come and see me a lot at EBICHU.
Bye bye.